[{"question": "What do you do to prepare for your games?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 33, "answers": [{"answer": "Play some good music to get pumped up!", "points": ["energetic"]}, {"answer": "Spend some time practicing by myself.", "points": ["lonely", "easygoing"]}, {"answer": "Crack jokes with my teammates to ease the tension.", "points": ["goofy", "mischievous"]}, {"answer": "Nothing. I just take each game as it comes.", "points": ["reckless", "carefree"]}]}, {"question": "What's your immediate feeling upon receiving the ball from the other team?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 34, "answers": [{"answer": "Jazzed!", "points": ["carefree", "energetic"]}, {"answer": "Nervous...", "points": ["anxious"]}, {"answer": "Angry!", "points": ["brash", "tough"]}, {"answer": "Shook...", "points": ["dramatic", "gentle"]}]}, {"question": "The other team is trash talking you. How do you respond?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 35, "answers": [{"answer": "Trash talk them back!", "points": ["brash", "dramatic"]}, {"answer": "Play a prank on them!", "points": ["mischievous", "goofy"]}, {"answer": "Let it slide.", "points": ["carefree", "easygoing", "calm"]}]}, {"question": "Who are you picking to join your team?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 36, "answers": [{"answer": "Someone who suits our strengths and weaknesses.", "points": ["serious"]}, {"answer": "Someone who's a proven team player and good sport.", "points": ["kind"]}, {"answer": "Someone I'm close with and can trust.", "points": ["shy", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "You've decided to create new team uniforms! What style are you going for?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 37, "answers": [{"answer": "Something loud and flashy!", "points": ["passionate", "dramatic"]}, {"answer": "Something cute!", "points": ["jolly", "kind"]}, {"answer": "Something safe and unassuming.", "points": ["calm", "serious", "anxious"]}]}, {"question": "Would you rather be besties or rivals with a teammate?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 38, "answers": [{"answer": "Besties! I'm all about good vibes!", "points": ["gentle", "easygoing", "passionate", "kind"]}, {"answer": "Rivals! I like a little friendly competition!", "points": ["brash", "dramatic", "tough", "mischievous"]}]}, {"question": "You made a game-losing misplay! What do you do about it?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 39, "answers": [{"answer": "Laugh it off and take it in stride! It's part of the game.", "points": ["energetic", "jolly"]}, {"answer": "Study the replay intensely and ensure this never happens again.", "points": ["logical", "passionate"]}, {"answer": "Play it back a hundred times in my head while lying awake at 2 AM.", "points": ["anxious", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "That game was a disaster, and your teammate is feeling down. What do you say to them?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 40, "answers": [{"answer": "\"We'll get 'em next time for sure!\"", "points": ["passionate"]}, {"answer": "\"You did great. I'm proud of you!\"", "points": ["gentle", "kind"]}, {"answer": "\"Ugh, that game SUCKED, huh?\"", "points": ["dramatic"]}, {"answer": "\"I hope our next game goes better...\"", "points": ["anxious"]}]}, {"question": "You're being interviewed about a recent game. How do you give your answers?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 41, "answers": [{"answer": "Play it straight.", "points": ["serious", "shy"]}, {"answer": "Mix some humor into my responses.", "points": ["goofy"]}]}, {"question": "What type of play are you best at?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 42, "answers": [{"answer": "A powerful spike to the other team!", "points": ["tough", "reckless"]}, {"answer": "A careful set to my teammate!", "points": ["gentle", "jolly"]}, {"answer": "A cunning support play!", "points": ["mischievous"]}, {"answer": "A tactical defensive play!", "points": ["anxious", "logical"]}]}, {"question": "Your teammate compliments you in the locker room after a game! How do you respond?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 43, "answers": [{"answer": "Smile and thank them!", "points": ["brash"]}, {"answer": "Compliment them back!", "points": ["kind"]}, {"answer": "I'd be too shy to respond...", "points": ["shy"]}]}, {"question": "How would you congratulate a teammate after a great game?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 44, "answers": [{"answer": "A high-five!", "points": ["passionate", "shy"]}, {"answer": "A fist bump!", "points": ["tough", "reckless"]}, {"answer": "A hug!", "points": ["gentle", "kind"]}]}, {"question": "What's your favorite location for a match of Beastieball?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 45, "answers": [{"answer": "Under the shade in a grassy glade!", "points": ["gentle", "goofy"]}, {"answer": "The summit of a snowy mountain!", "points": ["tough"]}, {"answer": "The sea, on a giant Tortanchor's back!", "points": ["energetic", "reckless"]}, {"answer": "A dark, abandoned mine!", "points": ["mischievous", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "What type of Beastieball game do you prefer?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 46, "answers": [{"answer": "A short, fast-paced scramble!", "points": ["goofy", "brash", "dramatic"]}, {"answer": "A long, drawn out match with lots of strategy!", "points": ["spacey", "logical", "calm"]}, {"answer": "Something in the middle.", "points": ["lonely", "jolly"]}]}, {"question": "You've just won an important game! What are you doing with your team to celebrate?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 47, "answers": [{"answer": "A nice dinner!", "points": ["easygoing"]}, {"answer": "Ice cream for everyone!", "points": ["jolly"]}, {"answer": "A fun activity, like bowling!", "points": ["energetic"]}, {"answer": "Relax and get some well-needed rest.", "points": ["gentle", "lonely"]}]}, {"question": "You're playing in the final game of the season. The stakes are high, and you're about to make the game-winning move... How do you play it?", "sortOrder": 1, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 48, "answers": [{"answer": "Give it all I've got! Spike it as hard as I can!", "points": ["brash", "passionate", "reckless"]}, {"answer": "Take it easy, so I don't mess it up.", "points": ["anxious", "calm", "gentle", "spacey"]}, {"answer": "Set it to my teammate, so they can make the play.", "points": ["kind", "jolly", "dramatic"]}]}, {"question": "If your team had a theme song, what would it be like?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 49, "answers": [{"answer": "Uplifting and triumphant!", "points": ["passionate"]}, {"answer": "Catchy and fun!", "points": ["jolly", "carefree"]}, {"answer": "Tense and imposing!", "points": ["tough", "serious", "dramatic"]}, {"answer": "Smooth jazz.", "points": ["goofy", "easygoing"]}]}, {"question": "It's time to pick a Platinum Sponsor for your team! What's the most important factor for you?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 50, "answers": [{"answer": "How well-known they are, and whether or not that reputation is good.", "points": ["kind"]}, {"answer": "How much are they gonna pay us? That's all that really matters!", "points": ["reckless"]}, {"answer": "Whether or not their name sounds funny.", "points": ["mischievous"]}]}, {"question": "How would you describe your vibe on the court?", "sortOrder": 0, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 51, "answers": [{"answer": "I play to hype up my teammates!", "points": ["passionate", "jolly"]}, {"answer": "I play to keep the other team guessing!", "points": ["goofy", "mischievous"]}, {"answer": "I play to get the crowd and my coach fired up!", "points": ["brash", "dramatic"]}, {"answer": "Nothing in particular; I just play the way I play.", "points": ["calm", "carefree", "shy"]}]}, {"question": "What would you say is your most defining attribute?", "sortOrder": 2, "shuffleAnswers": false, "index": 52, "answers": [{"answer": "^Body`.", "points": ["dramatic", "reckless", "tough", "energetic", "easygoing", "brash"]}, {"answer": "&Spirit`.", "points": ["anxious", "carefree", "goofy", "jolly", "kind", "passionate", "shy"]}, {"answer": "*Mind`.", "points": ["calm", "logical", "lonely", "serious", "spacey", "gentle", "mischievous"]}]}]